本字幕由 ShinY 深影字幕组 原创翻译制作
深影字幕组论坛地址 http://shinybbs.com
翻译： shadow 水涟漪 Saturnine 魔法莉露姆
校对： 闲鱼  后期： 小安
邻里又不得安宁了
Just another day in the neighbourhood.
继续开枪!
Keep firing!
我们可以用其他方法
It didn't have to go like this.
耶茨 不要坐那 朝他们开枪
Yates, don't just sit there, return fire!
该我们了!
Let's go!
安琪尔! 他中枪了 罗素
Angel! He's hit Russell.
狗娘养的
Son of a bitch.
你怎么不掩护他?
Why the hell weren't you covering him?
你还好吗 伙计?
You're good, okay.
掩护我
Cover me.
他中枪了! 他中枪了!
He's down! He's down!
待着别动
Stay here.
卧底游戏 第一季 第九集
你知道这东东太棒了
You know this thing is amazing.
我可以随心所欲的调整相机感光度
I can push my ISO like crazy.
我可以在壁橱里拍照
I could shoot in a closet
这样就完全不会有噪音了
and there would be zero noise.
好了 别拍了
Come on.
你应该让我给你拍完 你真是帅呆了
You should let me take your picture, you're a beautiful man.
我让你拍过 在墨西哥戴着墨西哥帽
I do let you; that one time in Mexico wearing the sombrero.
我想起来了 你喝醉了望着我出神
Yeah and you were drunk and mooning me.
快去工作吧
Go to work.
你害怕相机会泄漏你内心的秘密
You're scared the camera's gonna reveal your deep dark secrets to me.
我说的对吗?
Am I right?
如果你发现我是个烂人怎么办?
What happens if you find out what a terrible person I am?
那看我运气了
I'll take my chances.
再见
Bye.
晚上见
See you tonight.
反黑组  负责调查枪支和帮派案件
The SMASH unit. Guns and Gangs.
我们认为里面可能有猫腻
We think there could be a coverup.
反黑组发起枪战
SMASH guys initiated the shoot out.
理由并不充分
We're not convinced they had cause.
我们关注他们有一段时间了
We've been concerned with this unit for some time.
包括作战策略 武力使用
Their tactics, their use of force.
那为什么还让他们执行任务呢?
So why haven't you pulled them from duty?
因为还没有足够的证据
We haven't been able to prove anything.
这就是我找你们的原因
That's where you come in.
这个家伙是一个犯案累累的恶棍
This guy was a veteran banger,
背负了八条罪行 毒品买卖 故意伤害
Eight convictions. Trafficking, aggravated assault.
等等 你们想调查反黑组?
Wait a second, you're actually going to go after the SMASH unit?
你们认为这样做很聪明吗?
You think that's wise?
他们可是功勋卓著的警察
These guys are decorated cops.
几乎算得上是警界的摇滚明星了
They're pretty much rock stars.
那我确信你们不会有任何发现
Then I'm sure you won't find anything.
如果我们有发现呢? 他们人脉很广
And if we do? They're also well connected.
CIU刚刚成立不久 这会毁了我们的
The CIU is still a new unit, this could finish us.
你们的存在就是为了接手这样的任务
An assignment like this is why you're in the budget.
丽贝卡 这次任务没有讨价还价的余地
It isn't up for debate, Rebecca.
如果你认为这些人没有撒谎
If you think these guys aren't lying,
那就去证明
then prove it.
丹尼尔就是从那出来的 你知道是吗?
That's Daniel's old unit, you know that right?
你说真的吗? 我们要和内务部合作?
You're serious? We're working with Internal Affairs?
关于调查其他警察不是有规定的吗?
Isn't there like a rule about looking into other cops?
是的 规定是你不能这么做
Yeah, the rule is: You don't do it.
甚至想都不能想
You don't even think about it.
丹尼尔 你和他们共事过
Daniel, you ran with these guys.
给我们介绍一下?
You want to set it up?
在反黑组
The SMASH unit.
我和一些最好的警察合作
Some of the best cops I've worked with.
他们横扫大街小巷 进行大量的逮捕行动
They pound the streets. They make a ton of arrests.
偶尔有些莽撞
Sometimes they get a little cowboy,
不是每个人都能理解他们的做法
not everyone understands that.
特别是内务部
Especially Internal Affairs.
安琪尔・阿巴诺 其中一个成员
Angel Abano, one of their guys.
在这次枪击事件中受伤
He was injured during the shoot out.
他们需要有人来顶替他
They need someone to take his place.
杰西是最佳人选
That's going to be Jesse.
他是新来的 他们肯定不认识他
He's new, they won't know him.
丹尼尔 你协助杰西准备
Daniel, I'm going to list you as a reference;
一些书面材料
on Jesse's paperwork
我需要你都准备好
I need you to set it up.
如果我拒绝呢?
What if I refuse?
那你可以从交通部给我打电话
Then you can give me a call from traffic duty,
提醒我在三十度的高温下那身警服多么难受
remind me how itchy that poly blend is in 80 degree heat.
关于这件事你们谁都没有我难受
None of you get to act like you're any more upset about this than I am.
但我们的工作是找出真相
Our job is to find out the truth.
关于枪击他们究竟有没有撒谎?
Are they lying about the shooting?
如果说了谎 那事实是什么?
If so, what really happened out there?
如果他们是清白的 我们就找出证据
If they're clean, we prove it and
内务部也会撤销调查
IA steps down.
就像处理其他案件一样
We treat this like any other case.
杰西
Jesse.
好吧 听着
Alright, listen up.
罗素・哈格勒 是反黑组的老大
Russell Hagler, he runs the unit.
你需要让他记住你
He's the one you need to impress,
他是整件事情的关键
he's the key to this whole thing.
你们两个关系很好?
You two were close?
没错
Yeah.
罗素是我的导师 我们在一起三年
Russell was my mentor; three years.
他就像我的兄长
He's like a big brother.
那个家伙呢?
What about that guy?
他是罗素的得力助手 凯文・耶茨
That's Russell's right-hand man; Kevin Yates.
他是个好人 好警察
He's a good guy, real police.
好吧 我们去告诉丽贝卡你准备好了
Alright, let's go tell Rebecca you're ready.
丹尼尔会安排杰西和他们认识
Daniel will set up the first introduction.
反黑组的人总去同一个酒吧
The SMASH guys always drink at the same bar;
我们就在那行动
we'll do it on their home turf.
杰西需要给他们留下好印象
Jesse needs to make a good first impression,
能否打入反黑组就看这了
his entry into the unit depends on it.
丹尼尔做好掩护
Daniel will run cover.
我希望每个人都拿出最好的表现来
I want everyone on their A game.
进展越快
The faster we move,
这件事就越早结束
the faster we can close the book on this.
耶 龙舌兰酒!
Yeah, tequila!
我一直在想 我们都是警察
I keep thinking, we're cops,
应该相互保护
we're supposed to protect each other.
没错 继续这么想
Yeah, you keep thinking that.
听着 他们有时会测试你 明白吗?
Look, at some point, they're going to test you, okay?
这是一种入会测试 随机应变就好了
It's an initiation. Just roll with it, okay?
你呢 准备好了吗?
What about you. You up for this?
是的 轮到我倒霉
Hell yeah, time of my damn life.
浪子回头金不换
The prodigal son returns.
我一走近就闻到怪味
I knew I smelled something when I walked in here.
你口臭还没好 嗯庞兹?
You still got that halitosis problem, eh Pounds?
你给我个热吻就知道了
Why don't you gimme a kiss, and you'll find out.
你确定今晚没有任务吗?
Sure tonight's not gonna be too much action for you?
真希望你能和我们痛饮几杯 老朋友
Hope you're up for some drinking, my friend.
这是杰西・波顿 刚从安大略警察学校毕业
Here he is, Jesse Borden, straight out of OPC.
班里的高材生 警校中的佼佼者
Hotshot of his class. The academy's best kept secret.
是吗?
Is that so?
你还没有解释为什么想加入我们组
Doesn't explain why you wanna be in my unit.
我从小就立志帮助人民
Ever since I was a kid. I wanted to help people.
保护人民
Protect them.
无意冒犯 孩子
Well, no offense kid,
但我们追逐的是大街上的垃圾
but we chase street waste.
你想拯救人民 应该去当护士
You wanna save people, go be a nurse.
嘿 你淡定些
Hey, you gotta settle down.
还没正式加入这小子就要被你吓跑了
You're gonna scare the kid off before we even started.
丹尼小子 你看起来很好
You look good, Danny Boy.
过来 我请你喝一杯
C'mon, I'll buy you a drink.
你要过来坐下吗?
You gonna sit down?
泰瑞怎么样?
How's Terri?
自从我加入凶杀组之后我们就没见过
You haven't seen me since I took homicide,
你还认为我和同一个女人在一起?
and you automatically think I'm with the same woman?
今年冬天我们就要结婚了
We're getting married this winter.
还是我认识的丹尼・普莱斯
Same old Danny Price.
我见过的最忠诚的男人
Most loyal guy I've ever known.
嘿 伙计 安琪尔怎么样?
Hey look man, how's Angel?
他恢复的很好 他很坚强
He's doing alright, he's tough.
你听说耶茨要退休了吗?
You hear Yates is retiring?
是吗?
Yeah?
他年纪大了 行动也缓慢了
He's getting old and soft.
我需要新鲜血液
I need somebody young.
这个杰西看起来有些娘娘腔
This Jesse kid looks straight laced.
你觉得他合适吗?
Is he going to fit in?
他还不错 争强好斗 我认识他哥哥
He's good, scrappy. I know his brother.
不要被这个帅小伙的表面迷惑
Don't let the pretty boy routine fool you.
他可不好惹
He's a tough kid.
杰西 喝完它 这都是免费的
Drink up, Jesse, they're on the house.
他们知道我们是警察?
They know we're cops?
小子 这儿每个人都知道我们是谁
Kid, everybody here knows who we are.
我们给杰西准备一间公寓
We'll set up a cover apartment for Jesse.
监听装置已经安好了
It'll be fully wired.
卡丽负责安装摄像头和麦克
Khali will set up cameras and mics.
覆盖整个住所
Full coverage.
耶茨肯定有问题
There's something going on with Yates.
他在隐瞒什么
He's hiding something.
我被他盯上了
I got a hit off him.
你是团队里的新人
You're the new guy on the team.
他们所有人都会观察你
They're going to be watching you, all of them.
我不知道
I don't know,
耶茨给人感觉不一样 他更紧张
Yates felt different, he's more intense.
那你多关注他一下 这样行吗?
Then you keep an eye on him, alright?
不要乱说话
Don't make up stories.
嘿 你过来
Hey, come here.
我希望你对他说话客气点
I want you to go easy on him.
如果他告诉你他被盯上了
If he tells you he got a hit,
你听着就是
you listen.
我现在不需要你鼓舞士气
I don't need a pep talk right now.
你是不是有什么事瞒着我?
Is there something you're not telling me?
公事公办 我们干活儿就是了
It's business. Let's just do the job.
嘿
Hey.
去睡会吧
Get some sleep.
你还好吗?
How you doing?
好多了
I've been better.
所有的摄像头和麦克已经安装好了
I've got cameras and mics in place.
明天就可以用了
They'll be up by tomorrow.
完全覆盖 除了...
Full coverage, everything except...
除了卧室?
Except bedroom?
晚安 杰西
Good night, Jesse.
嘿
Hey.
我很想你
I miss you.
你需要休息
You need to sleep.
我要马上离开这 不然又会做出蠢事来
And I need to get out of here before I do something stupid.
有空聊  好吗?
Talk to you later, okay?
卡丽
Khali.
想出去兜兜风吗?
You feel like taking a ride?
嘿 怎么了?
Hey, what's going on?
今晚有任务?
We working tonight?
嘿 你们这是做什么?
Hey, what are you doing?
没事的
This won't hurt a bit.
我没让你动别动
Don't move until I tell you.
你以为你突然冒出来就可以加入我们组?
So, think you can just show up out of nowhere and join my unit?
小子 这次是玩真的
This is the real deal, kid.
你有这个本事在这吗?
You got what it takes to be here?
我想我有
I think so.
不 你或者是有 或者没有
No, you either do or you don't!
去你妈的
Screw you.
很好 这才像样
Good. That's more like it.
那间屋里有三公斤海洛因
There are three kilos of H inside that house,
或许更多
maybe more.
你进去找出来拿给我
You're going to go in there and get it for me.
有搜查令吗?
What about a warrant?
不要担心这个 我们都准备好了
Don't worry about that, we've got it covered.
快去!
Move!
你想加入反黑组 就要学会随机应变
You want to run with SMASH, learn to improvise.
现在快去
Now go.
随机应变
Improvise
警察!
Police!
别动!
Don't move!
我们拿到搜查令来搜查你的住所 把枪放下
We have a warrant to search the premises. Put the weapon down
你们不能闯入我的房子
You can't just come into my house.
得了 安德烈 你还是老实点
C'mon, Andre, be a good boy;
告诉我们毒品在哪
Tell us where the drugs are.
死去吧 除非我见到搜查令
Screw you man, not till I see your warrant.
你想看我的搜查令 安德烈?
You wanna see my warrant, Andre?
我看看我能不能找到 哈哈
Let's just see if I can find my warrant, huh.
不 不在这
Nope. Not here.
嘿 嘿! 不要碰
Hey, hey! Don't touch that.
那是我妈妈的东西
That was my mom's stuff.
哎呀
Whoops.
罗素 你怎么看
What do you think, Russell?
我该放过这玩意儿吗
Should I leave this stuff alone?
你晓得我们为何而来
You know what we came for.
好吧
All right.
来啊 安德烈 毒品在哪里
Come on, Andre, where are the drugs?
别别别 放过它 别碰它
No, no, no. Leave that alone, don't touch it.
伙计 你们在干嘛
What are you doing man?
你刚说这曾是你妈妈的东西
You said this was your mom's stuff.
那这一定就是你妈妈喽
This must be your mom, then.
把它放下
Put that down.
快放下
Put it down.
我就把它放在这里
I'll put it right over here.
你觉得这东西能漂多远 安德烈
How far down you think this thing goes, Andre?
想猜猜吗
You wanna take a guess?
来呦 毒品在哪儿
C'mon, where's the drugs?
你最好告诉他 安德烈
You better tell him, Andre.
住手
Stop!
她在这里
There she goes.
不要
No!
放聪明点
Be smart.
拿不到东西我们不会走的
We're not leaving without the stuff.
你想搞得多困难 随你的便
It's up to you how hard you wanna make this.
好吧 你是头儿
Okay, you're the boss.
好吧好吧
Okay! Okay! Okay!
我告诉你们 快住手吧
I'll tell you. Just stop!
啥
What?
就在空调后面 全部都在
It's in the air conditioner out back. All of it.
把它给我
Give me that.
哈哈 妈妈的乖宝宝
Ha ha, Mama's boy.
你有病 孩子 你知道吧
You're sick, kid, you know that, right?
而你呢 则是幸运地逃过一劫
And you, you're getting off lucky.
耶茨 你可找到我们了
Yates, you found us.
我还以为今晚不会这么做的
I thought we weren't doing this tonight.
那好 我忘记给你打电话了
Yeah well, I guess I forgot to call you.
今晚这里发生的事
What went on here tonight,
喜欢不
you like it?
是不是你的作风
Is that your style?
- 我只是在做本分工作 - 是吗
- I was just doing my job, man. - Yeah?
只会越来越糟
It only gets worse from here.
最好做好准备
You better get ready.
昨晚反黑组强闯民宅
So last night, SMASH unit broke into a civilian's house,
又打又砸 暴力胁迫房主
trashed it, and threatened him with violence.
却没有提出一项指控
They didn't lay a single charge.
瞧 我不知道会这么失控
Look, I don't know it would get out of hand like that.
他只是试着恐吓罗素 奏效了
He was trying to impress Russell, and it worked.
是个入会测试 杰西出色地通过了
It was an initiation and Jesse passed, with flying colors.
昨晚发生的事很好 他加入了
What happened last night was good. He's in.
我们想努力证明反黑组在照章办事
We're trying to prove the unit's doing things by the book.
如果昨晚的任何迹象
If last night's any indication...
昨晚什么也说明不了
Last night doesn't prove anything.
有时候你得打破规矩 那些人懂
Sometimes you gotta bend the rules. These guys know that.
你是在告诉我你会闯进别人家
You're telling me you would go into someone's house,
破坏财产 施以威胁吗
damage their property, threaten them.
我会 如果有必要
Yes I would, if I had to.
三公斤海洛因今天早上被查获
Three kilos of heroin went into lock up early this morning,
反黑组
care of SMASH unit.
好现象?
Silver lining?
二把手 耶茨 突袭的时候他不在
The second in command, Yates. He wasn't there for the raid.
之后才来
Showed up later.
你说过他们之间关系有点紧张?
You said there was tension?
非常紧张
Big time.
好吧
All right.
有分歧了 要是他们不和 罗素就会寻找同盟
That's a crack. If they're on the outs, Russell's going to be looking for allies.
我想要你密切关注 让他知道你很忠心
I want you to stay close, show him you're going to be loyal.
没必要让内务部的知道昨晚的行动
Hey, there's no reason to let IA know about last night's stunt.
别对我说你不担心
Don't tell me you're not concerned?
反黑组了解法律
The SMASH unit they know the law.
如有必要他们会稍微有点越线
They play in the grey when they need to.
丽贝卡 之前我也见过你越线行事
I've seen you bend rules before Rebecca.
别跟我提什么兄弟之谊
Don't give me the brotherhood speech.
我是警察 我知道什么叫互相保护
I'm a cop, I know what it means to protect each other.
接着该是"但是"了
And here comes the "But".
如果他们是这样做事的话
If this is how these guys operate,
你觉得他们不会掩盖非法枪杀吗?
you don't think they'd cover up an illegal shooting?
你知道 你现在参与了谋杀
You're part of a murder now, you know.
你通过了测试
You passed the test.
你说"谋杀"是什么意思
What are you talking about a "murder"?
你知道人们都以为老鹰很厉害
You know everybody thinks eagles are baddass '
因为它们独自飞翔
cause they fly alone,
但是它们抓不了乌鸦
but they got nothing on crows.
你单独行动就会挂掉
You fly alone, you get yourself killed.
反黑组 像乌鸦一样追杀猎物
The unit, is like a murder of crows.
乌鸦们在一起决定他人的命运
Crows'll gather to decide the capital fate of another.
有自己的规矩
Make their own laws.
我们是和地头蛇对抗 我们赢不了 杰西
We're in a war against the streets, we can't win, Jesse.
你得选择站在哪边
You gotta choose which side of the battle you're on.
给你 双份奶油 双份糖
Here, double cream, double sugar.
警察 不许动
Hey! Police don't move!
你不知道自己在干什么 兄弟
You don't know what you're doing, man.
看起来你被抓到非法持有毒品
It looks like I got you on unlawful possession.
你不会想这样
You don't want to do that.
这个呢 非法持有毒品 意图贩卖
And what's this? Possession for the purposes of.
杰西 住手
Jesse, you've gotta stop.
放他走
Let him go.
你开玩笑吧
Are you serious?
他这儿有三克 我在他内裤里找到了点三八
He's got like 3 grams here; I just found a .38 in his underwear.
这么少 根本不值得我们花时间拘捕他
That little bit? Time we spend processing this guy.
你想告诉我罗素发生么神经
You wanna tell me what the hell's going on with Russell?
我很想告诉你怎么回事
I'd like to coach,
不过我自己现在也看不明白了
but I'm pretty much in the dark myself.
上车 别动
Get in the car. Don't move.
看见没 他把他的枪还回去了
You see this? He just gave him his gun back.
我去抓那小子
I'm bringing the kid in.
你跟着杰西
You stay with Jesse.
卢卡斯・史密斯, 也称作 卢克宝贝
Lucas Smith, AKA Baby Luke.
在少管所呆过一段时间 三年内没有被抓过
Did a stint in juvie, no arrests in 3 years.
是马尔沃黑帮的知名成员
Known member of the Marvo Crew.
是反黑组所管辖区内最大的黑帮
Which is the biggest gang in the SMASH unit's jurisdiction.
如果真有那么大 怎么几乎没有逮捕记录
If they're so big how come there are hardly any arrests in here?
马尔沃黑帮非法的行当经营的不错
The Marvo Crew run a pretty good racket
反黑组睁一只眼闭一只眼
Must be nice to move all that dope,
毒品运输一定畅通无阻
while SMASH unit looks the other way.
你给他们多少钱
How much you pay them?
反黑组 反黑组是什么?
SMASH, what's SMASH?
我不知道你在说什么 女士
I don't know what you're talking about, lady.
不知道 那为什么今天他们在你身上
No? Then why did they let you walk
找到枪支毒品还放你走了
when they found drugs and a gun on you today?
没让我走多远 我现在不是在这儿吗
Didn't let me walk far, I'm in here aren't I?
是我的人抓你的 不是反黑组
It was my people who brought you in, not SMASH.
说吧 卢克 你给那些警察多少钱
C'mon, Luke, how much are you paying those cops?
一定得让他们觉得值得 对吧
It's got to be enough to make it worth their while, right?
我没什么好说的
I've got nothing to say to you
你们干嘛不趁现在去把我律师找来呢?
so why don't you run and get my lawyer now?
好消息是你不需要律师
See, that's the good news. You don't need a lawyer.
我们要放了你
We're going to let you go.
不过首先我们会给反黑组打个电话
But first we're gonna put a call into the SMASH guys
告诉他们你说了什么
and tell them what you said.
你怎么说他们的
How you told us all about them.
他们怎么受贿 还有他们的非法勾当
How they're taking bribes, how they're dirty...
我可什么也没说啊
I didn't say any of that.
那好 那就坐着好好看着
Okay. We'll just sit back and watch.
你不必告发他们
You don't have to rat them out.
我们来看看他们怎么收拾你
We just wait to see what they do to you.
那就是我们的证据 对吧
And that will be our evidence, right?
好吧好吧 我接受指控 承认有罪
All right look, I'll take the charge, plead guilty,
你们想怎样都行 就是别
whatever you want. All right just...
拜托 别这样
please, don't do this.
你真的这么怕他们
You're really that afraid of them?
你得告诉我原因
You need to tell me why.
我会找人护送你出去 来吧
I'll get someone to escort you out of here. Come on.
放开我 等等 好啦
Let me go! Wait. Alright!
你放出话我是告密者
You put it out there I'm a rat
那他们两方都会想让我死
they're both gonna want me dead.
两方
Both?
这是什么意思
What's that supposed to mean?
你们还不懂吗
Don't you get it?
他们是合作的
They're working together.
警察和马尔沃黑帮他们是一伙的
Those cops and the Marvo Crew, they partnered up.
穿一条裤子
They're working the hood together.
反黑组是真正的老大
SMASH is running the whole show.
好吧 坐下
Alright, sit down.
跟紧我 杰西 我会照顾你
Stick with me, Jesse, I'll take care of you.
我能成为你最好的朋友 别忘了这个
I can be your best friend, don't forget that.
看看这些人 M3青年军 曾经统治这一带
See these guys, M3 Colts. Used to run this neighborhood,
直到我们来把他们赶走
before we came in and cleaned it up.
这么想抓捕罪犯? 我们就去抓一个
Wanna make an arrest so badly? Let's make one.
我们在这儿没事 罗素 没事
We're good here, Russell, it's fine.
这些人什么都没带
These guys are clean.
我可不这么想
Doesn't look fine to me.
杰西 检查一下后座
Jesse, check the backseat,
告诉我发现了什么
tell me what you see.
罗素 你在干什么
What are you doing, Russell?
什么也没有
Nothing in there.
真的
Really?
真的啊 罗素
Really now, Russell.
这是什么
What's this?
祝贺了 孩子
Congrats, kid.
你可以进行你的第一次抓捕行动了
You get to make your first arrest.
我真受够了内务部的人四处找茬
I was pissed enough that Internal Affairs was poking around,
- 然后我接到你的电话 - 先生
- then I get your call. - Sir.
你有一点概念
Do you have any idea...
那个枪击案有问题 长官
The shooting wasn't clean, sir.
反黑组和一个叫做马尔沃黑帮的帮派结盟
The SMASH unit is allied with a gang, the Marvo Crew.
他们是为了地盘才杀死了那孩子
They shot that kid over turf.
你怎么知道的?
You know this, how?
某个下三滥的毒贩子告诉你的?
Some scumbag drug dealer told you?
我是说那孩子希望和你做交易丽贝卡
I mean the kid's looking for a deal, Rebecca.
指控四个警察是自杀行动 不是交易
Accusing four cops is a suicide play, not a deal.
我的人看见罗素・哈格勒把武器还给帮派成员
My guys witnessed Russell Hagler returning a weapon to a gang member.
我现在就能逮捕他
I could arrest him right now.
我和你一样不喜欢这样做
Look, I hate this as much as you do.
你想借我的手来做 所以你才给我打电话?
You want to hand this off to me, is that why you called?
不是的 先生 我想追查下去
No sir, I want to pursue it.
如果我们不的话 我们也是纵容他们
If we don't, we're choosing to look the other way.
兄弟情谊也是有限度的
There's a point where the brotherhood ends.
你得到的消息可能没有任何意义
The information you've come across could be nothing.
不是这样的
It isn't.
不管你的人看见什么
Whatever your guys think they saw...
我们都不知道情况
we don't know what that was.
这么说以想把这事压下去?
So you're planning to bury this?
小心
Hey, careful.
要是你追查 结果你错了
If you pursue this, and you're wrong?
你就死定了
You'll go down, hard.
这个行动组 你的事业
This unit, your career,
你以为你知道的事情 都没了
whatever you thought you knew, will be gone.
长官 无意冒犯您
Due respect, sir,
你该想想如果我是对的怎么办?
you need to start thinking about what could happen if I'm right.
如果你对了 我会保护你
If you're right, I'll protect you.
但是到现在为止 侦探长
But so far, Detective Sergeant?
我还还是不相信
I'm unconvinced.
你觉得卢克孩子说的是真的
You think that kid Luke's telling the truth?
反黑组和马尔沃一起干
SMASH is working with the Marvos.
看起来是的
Looks that way, yeah.
所有人到简报室集合 立刻
I want everyone in briefing, now.
你要想想你的声誉 你以后的警察生涯
You need to think about your reputation, your future as cops.
你们自己决定
It's your decision.
如果你要抓其他警察 这事会跟你一辈子
If you go after other police, that's going to stick.
那么这卢克小子说的话就是铁板钉钉了
So this Luke kid, his word is iron clad?
丹尼尔 你亲眼看见罗素把武器还给那小子
Daniel, you watched Russell hand that weapon back to that kid yourself.
杰西看见他用毒品栽赃
Jesse saw him planting drugs.
那我们为什么不去抓他?
So why aren't we picking him up?
因为我想拿下所有人 一网打尽
Because I want them all. The entire unit.
我不强迫你 做不做由你
I'm not ordering you to do this. It's up to you.
从现在开始
From this point on,
你自己决定要不要继续跟进这个案子
if you move forward with this operation it's because you chose to.
好的 我们支持你
Alright, so we're with you.
好
Okay.
我们确信Smash跟马尔沃黑帮同流合污
We believe that SMASH is in bed with The Marvo Crew.
卢克说  马尔沃进出无碍
According to Luke, the Marvos get a free pass.
他们的死对头 M3青年军 每次都被抓
Their rivals, the M3 Colts, get nailed every time.
他们每次拿到毒品
Part of what they seize,
就拿一部分去街上二次售卖
they re-sell on the streets.
其他的屯起来
The rest goes into lock up.
那真是一大笔钱啊
That's a lot of drug money.
耶茨怎么样? 他很不开心
So what about Yates? He's unhappy.
他马上就要离开反黑组了
He's already leaving the unit.
也许是让他帮我们的好机会
Could mean he's ready to flip.
我们得跟他取得联系
We need to reach out to him.
罗素死死盯着我  我没法接近耶茨
Russell's all over me. I can't get near Yates.
那我呢?
What if I can?
听着 这里才是我的行动组 不是反黑组
Look, this is my unit, not SMASH.
我们动手吧
Let's do this.
我还以为只有女孩才抽这种烟
I thought only girls smoked those.
你嫉妒我 因为我抽的很爽
You're just jealous 'cause I make these look good.
你就自欺欺人吧 最近怎么样?
Yeah you keep telling yourself that. What's going on?
看见杰西没? 我联系不到他
You seen Jesse? I tried calling him.
他跟罗素一起 我们很快就要分队了
He's with Russell, we got squad soon.
你应该少喝点 马上就要当班了
No. You should go easy, you got shift soon.
少来啦
Takes the edge off.
听说你快退休了
I heard you were retiring man.
我还记得当年你为这个组奋不顾身的时候
I remember when this unit meant everything to you.
你不也是这样
Used to mean something to you too.
离开没那么容易 相信我
It wasn't easy walking away. Trust me.
做事张狂 为了干掉一些混蛋惹了一堆人
Going a little too far, kicking some ass to get the bad guy.
现在不是这样了
It's not like that anymore.
我们已经越界了 丹尼
We crossed over, Danny.
一切都不能回头了
I should've done it back then.
就像你一样 划清了界限
Just like you. Drawn my line in the sand.
你现在就可以啊
You can do that now.
你以为我为什么要离开?
Why do you think I'm getting out?
你要是关心那个杰西 就快把他弄出来
You care about that kid Jesse, you'll get him out too.
嘿耶茨 发生什么事了吗
Hey Yates, is there something going on?
你跟罗斯之间是不是有什么问题
Is there something happening between you and Russ?
罗素 老地方见
是罗素
It's Russell.
我要走了
I gotta go.
等会等会 再呆一分钟
Hold on, hold on. Just a second.
到底怎么了
What's going on?
到底有什么事?
Is there something I need to know?
你好好看着杰西 好吧?
You keep an eye on Jesse, alright?
杰西 怎么了?
Jesse, what's happening?
M3青年军有个藏毒地点 罗素有线索
M3 Colts have a stash house. Russell got a tip.
他想在他们听到风声挪货之前
He wants to do a takedown now,
将他们一网打尽
before they catch wind and move the product.
好的 你盯着那批货
Alright you keep an eye on the drugs.
我通知丽贝卡 你告诉我地点
I'll call Rebecca. You gimme that location.
从前门进 这次我们一起行动
Front door. We stay together on this one.
你俩殿后 我跟耶茨带路
You two hang back, Yates and I will take the lead.
他们要进屋了
They're going in.
耶茨 上楼 快
Yates, upstairs, let's go.
杰西 走吧
Jesse, let's go! Come on.
别跟个缩头乌龟似的
Get your head out of your ass.
杰西在拖延时间 事情不对劲
Jesse's stalling, something's up.
耶茨!
Yates!
慢点 慢点
Easy, easy.
这他妈的怎么回事?
What the hell is going on?
他开枪打中了耶茨
He shot Yates.
波顿警官 你要跟我走一趟
Officer Borden. You need to come with me.
我对今天发生的事 有些疑问
I've got questions about what happened today.
我们得把他弄出来
We gotta get him out of there.
待在车里别动 我不想暴露他的身份
Stay in the car. I don't want to burn him.
我来处理这事
I've got this.
我申请保护杰西
I want Jesse protected.
- 答应我你们会保护他 -丽贝卡.
- Tell me you'll take care of him. - Rebecca.
如果查出他是警察伪装的卧底
If it gets out that he went undercover on cops,
那他这辈子都完了
it will chase him for the rest of his career.
你以为你在跟谁说话
Who the hell do you think you're talking to?
要么他能毫发无伤的离开这儿
Either he walks away from this unscathed,
不然我会让每个警员都知道
or I will personally make sure that everyone on this force knows
耶茨警员的死因是因为你不支持我
that the reason Detective Yates died is because you wouldn't back me.
你会因为这个下台 而不是我
You'll be going down for this, not me.
等的花都快谢了
It's been forever.
你觉得他在里面干嘛
How do you think he's doing in there?
先看看吧 他来了
We'll see. Here he comes now.
我觉得是罗素杀了他
I think Russell killed him.
他杀了耶茨然后把枪塞到
I think he shot Yates and planted the gun
在场的那个孩子手里栽赃他
on that kid at the scene.
他进屋搜查的方式
It was the way he was moving around in that room.
还有他脸上的表情
It was the way he looked.
你告诉他们这些了吗?
Did you tell them that?
没有 我不能指控别的警官
No, I can't just accuse another cop.
杰西 看着我
Jesse, look at me.
你必须确定
You gotta be sure.
是他干的 我确定
He did it. I'm sure.
耶茨想出来
Yates wanted out.
他要离开行动组
He was leaving the unit.
罗素觉得他要告发他们 我确信是这样
Russell thought he was gonna blow the whistle on them. I sure of it.
我们得马上重新取得卡尔弗特警官的证词
We'll retake Officer Calvert's statement immediately,
然后从那开始
and go from there.
你要很谨慎 你得抹掉他的名字
You're going to be discreet, you're going to take his name out of this.
你也知道的 这不可能
Come on, that's not going to happen.
他会死的很惨
He'll be crucified.
一个警察被指控谋杀另一个警察丽贝卡
A cop has been accused of murdering another cop, Rebecca.
这简直就是大丑闻
There's no way this doesn't get ugly.
哈里森教育巡查员
Staff Inspector Harrison...
无权处理 这案子归内务部调查丽贝卡
Has no authority here, this is IA's investigation, Rebecca.
不管杰西有没有看见
Either Jesse saw it or he didn't.
我都需要他的证词
I want his statement.
我们需要证据
We need proof.
我不会让杰西一人承担这事
I'm not putting Jesse out there on his own.
好的 那我们暗中支持
Alright, then we stay under.
在罗素听到风声之前 我们先拿下他
We get to Russell first, before he feels the heat.
丽贝卡让所有人都去简报室
Rebecca wants everybody in the briefing room.
让她等等
She can wait.
耶茨是我的朋友
Yates was a friend of mine.
这不可能
There's no way.
罗素会做很多事 但他不可能做这件事
Russell is capable of a lot of things, but not that.
我知道我看见了什么
I know what I saw.
那你看到的就是错的
Then you saw wrong.
我告诉她你马上来
I'll tell her you're coming.
突袭行动当中 突然有人开枪 情况复杂
Middle of a raid, gunshots, things get foggy.
很难说你到底看到了什么  杰西
It's hard to know what exactly you saw, Jesse.
也许你是一叶障目
Maybe you've got tunnel vision.
这对你们来说很难接受 我懂
This is hard for you, I get that.
但如果杰西是对的 他就需要支援
But if Jesse's right, he needs backup.
他同样需要证据 他是这儿唯一有危险的人
He also needs proof. He's the one on the line here.
耶茨马上就要退休了
Yates was about to retire from the unit.
罗素担心他会告密
Russell was paranoid he was going to talk.
那我们就利用他的担心
Let's use that paranoia.
可能是我们最好的切入点
Could be our best way in.
丹尼尔你最了解罗素 你说该怎么做
Daniel, you know Russell the best. You tell us.
如果这事是真的
Look, if this is true,
或许杰西可以给他打电话
maybe Jesse can call him,
说他不想干了
tell him he wants out of the unit.
我们要让罗素感觉他失去控制权了
We need to make Russell feel like he's losing control.
他会担心杰西在突袭时看到了什么
He'll be worried what Jesse saw at the raid.
然后会想见他
He'll want to come see him.
好的杰西 你跟他谈 要坦诚
Okay Jesse, you talk to him, you got to open up.
告诉他你在房子里看到的情景让你很害怕
Tell him you're freaking out about what you saw in the house.
你必须要让他说 明白吗
You got to get him to talk, alright?
嘿
Hey.
你没事吧
You okay?
我没事
Yeah. I'm good.
那好 我们开工吧
Alright let's get to work.
你紧张吗
You nervous?
是啊
Yeah.
我也是
Me too.
再让我听听音频
Let me hear the audio again.
能说点什么吗? 我们好调音量
Can you say something? Give us a level.
罗素我一直在想
Russell, I've been thinking.
我想了好久 这工作并不适合我
I've been thinking it over, and it's not for me.
- 很好 - 好了 准备就绪
- That's good  - we're good. We're ready.
杰西
Jesse...
你能办好这事 知道吗?　你做得到
You' got this, okay? You can do it.
注意了
Heads up.
杰西　他们在门外了
Okay Jesse, they're coming to the door.
你一个人吗
You alone?
是啊
Yeah.
我知道发生那件事　很难受
I know what happened was tough, alright?
但这并不意味着你需要离开反黑组
But it doesn't mean you need to leave the unit.
我一直在想反黑组　想你们做的事
I been thinking about SMASH, what you guys do.
不太适合我
It's just not for me.
我们做的事?
What we do?
庞兹　他说我们做的事是什么意思?
Pounds, what's that mean, "What we do"?
真难倒我了　啥意思　小滑头
Beats me. What's that mean, Slick?
让我们把这事捋捋
So let me get this straight.
你想离开
You want to leave.
听着 杰西　我绝不会让这事发生
Look, Jesse, I can't let that happen.
不可能
Nope.
绝不可能　小Ｊ
No can do, J-bird.
罗素太偏执了　他不会好好谈的
Russell's too paranoid, he's not going to talk.
如果你真要离开
If you do leave,
我们别无选择　只好告诉大家真相
we have no chance but to tell everyone the truth.
真相
Truth?
关于你的真相
Truth about you.
我们今早去见了安德烈
See, we paid Andre a visit this morning.
关于那晚发生的事情　他记得很清楚
Turns out he remembers this night pretty clearly.
主要是你　你一脚踹开他家前门
Mostly you, you kicking in his front door,
在他面前挥舞着枪
waving a gun in his face.
没错　他记得很清楚
Yeah, he remembers that real clear.
我只是做了你们让我做的事
I was just doing what you guys told me to do.
我从没告诉你去恐吓别人
I never told you to intimidate anyone.
毁坏他的东西　我没告诉你这么做吧
Destroy his possessions. I didn't tell you that, did I?
那是严重的＂徽章综合症＂　你完全失控了
That's heavy badge syndrome. You couldn't be controlled.
罗素只是想给你个机会 　但你搞砸了
Russell was trying to give you a shot and you …you blew it.
事实上 我们跟你工作的这段时间
Fact is, the whole time we worked with you,
你都是闯入民宅 栽赃毒品
you were breaking into houses, planting drugs,
伪造报告
falsifying reports.
你的做法麻烦大了
Total behaviour problem.
现在 知道你打哪来的 一切都说得通了
Now, kinda makes sense, given where you came from.
我们看了你的档案 孩子 你在南部长大
Read your file, kid, you grew up in Southside.
一个孤独的渴望归属感的孩子 不是吗
Just another lonely kid looking to belong, right?
唯一的问题是
The only problem is
你只是一个祸害
you're nothing but trouble.
我真心希望你厌倦了做警察 杰西
I sure hope you're tired of being a cop, Jesse.
因为你完蛋了
Because you are done.
他在说什么
What's he talking about?
罗素不会透露任何信息
Russell's not going to give us anything.
他想要摧毁杰西的公信度
He's going to try to destroy Jesse's credibility.
那不可能站得住脚
That'll never stand up.
是吗? 看上去他好像把每个人都摸透了
Really? Look he's got the neighborhood under his thumb,
他们会替罗素出庭作证
they'll vouch for Russell.
他要干嘛
What's he doing?
丹尼尔 丹尼尔!
Daniel. Daniel!
他要进去了
He's going inside.
他在想什么?
What is he thinking?
不知道
I don't know.
你想干什么?
What are you doing?
我原本信任你的 你怎么能这样
I trusted you. How could you do this?
我们赶紧离开这吧 快点
Let's get the hell out of here man, we gotta go.
丹尼 发生什么了?
Danny. What the hell man?
跟我讲讲发生了什么
You going to tell me what's going on?
听我说 相信我 我们快点离开这
Listen to me. Just trust me, we gotta get out of here.
除非你告诉我发生了什么
No one goes anywhere until you tell me what's going on.
听着 我的这个哥们
Listen, I got a buddy,alright.
他一直监视着你们 然后通知了我
He's got his ear to the ground, and he gave me a call.
内务部 这小子是卧底 他是来调查你的
IA, the kid's on the job, he's working you.
听着 对不起 我搞砸了
Look, I'm sorry, I screwed up.
如果我知道他会这样
I would've never brought him near you,
我就不会把他带来你这边
if I knew.
怎么了罗素 你搞得我有点紧张
Yo, Russell, what's up, you're making me nervous over here.
这小子在调查我们
The kid's working us.
冷静点 哥们
Hey, come on man, calm down.
检查一下 我们被监视了
Check the place, it's wired.
在哪
Where is it?
在哪?
我不知道
I don't know.
罗素.
Russell.
你这狗娘养的
You little bitch.
我完了 丹尼
I'm screwed, Danny.
冷静点
Okay.
要是这小子看见你做了些出格的事情
So, what if the kid saw you get a little out of line.
你们也都知道我们会这么做 这是我们的工作
Everyone knows that's what we do, that's part of the job.
罗素 我们还等什么 快点走
Russell, what are we doing man; we should get out of here.
闭上你的嘴 别打扰我!
Shut up and let me think!
我得想一想 我得想一想
I just need to think. I just need to think.
你
You.
是你把这小子介绍来了
You introduced this kid to me.
罗素 我是来找你帮你摆平这事的
Russ, I came to find you, I came to make this go away.
我怎么知道你就不是来调查我的?
How do I know you're not wired?
得了吧
Russ. Come on!
巴蒂那伙人
The Bardi crew.
你还记得吗 八年前的事情
Eight years ago, you remember that?
我们办的那件大案子?
That big takedown we did?
还记得那个狂妄的家伙吗
Remember that guy that was mouthing off too much?
科斯塔・桑切斯.
Costa Sanchez.
你当时把他痛打了一顿 罗斯
You beat him up pretty bad, Russ.
他不久就死在了医院里
He ended up dying in hospital later.
但我没有上报这事
I didn't report that.
我保护了你
I protected you.
我们在录像 他不知道吗?
We're recording this. Does he know that?
丹尼尔到底想干嘛?
What the hell are you doing Daniel?
如果我这边在监听你们 我会说这些吗
And if I was wearing a wire would I say all of this?
我和你一样都有罪
I'm just as guilty as you.
罗斯 我们是兄弟 我以前就挺你
Russ, come on we're brothers, man. I had your back then.
现在不也是一样吗
Don't I have it now?
但你必须告诉我到底发生了什么
But you gotta talk to me, you gotta tell me what's going on Russell.
你干了什么?
What did you do?
罗斯 这到底怎么回事?
Russ, what the hell is going on?
- 我欠了很多债 - 钱?
- I'm in a lot of debt man. - Money?
所以你收了些不该收的钱?
So, you took some money you shouldn't have, man.
还有吗 我们都受过诱惑 还有别的吗
What else? We all get tempted. What else?
这里被监听了 罗素!
This place is wired. Russell!
现在无所谓了
It doesn't matter, not anymore.
他要泄密
He was going to squeal.
他会把我们全毁了的
He was going to hurt us. All of us.
我不得不让他消失 丹尼尔
Daniel, I needed him gone.
罗素!
Russell!
闭嘴
Shut up!
你说的是耶茨吗 罗素
Are you talking about Yates, Russell?
你开枪打了耶茨?
Russell, did you shoot Yates?
他说他不会就这样算了的
He told me he wasn't gonna let it go.
为了大家 我不得不这么做
I had to, for us, didn't I?
我心里真的很难受 丹尼尔
Daniel, I am in so deep man.
早知我就不该保护你
I shouldn't have protected you back then.
我打算逮捕你
I'm taking you in.
你难道觉得你就是个好人了?
You think you're better than me, is that it?
你也会这么做的
You would have done the same thing.
我们都一样
We are the same.
我们不一样
We're not the same.
现在不是
Not now.
以后也不是
Not ever.
嘿!
Hey.
丹尼尔怎么样
What happened with Daniel?
丹尼尔 在他在反黑组时还是个菜鸟
Daniel was a rookie cop when he was with SMASH.
太害怕了 不敢违抗他们的意思
A kid too scared to go against the force.
我对督察长这么为他辩护的
That was my argument, to the Chief Inspector.
好吧
Okay.
他相信了吗
And he bought it?
原本可能不会这样的
That could have gone a different way.
我有可能错了
I could've been wrong.
你们都和我一起插手这事情
You guys all followed me in,
而我并不一定是正确的
and I could've been wrong.
但你是没错
Yeah, but you weren't.
听着丽贝卡
Look, Rebecca,
你今天做的这些
what you did today.
得罪了警长 内务部 你把团队放在第一位
Taking on the brass. IA. You put your team first.
我没见过别的警察能做到这点
No other cop I know would have been able to do that.
只有你
No other cop,
有这样的勇气
would've had the strength.
罗素跟我说了有关街区里的事情
Russell said this thing to me.
我们所做的事情...
About the streets, what we do...
以及如何去打一场不可能胜利的战争
How we're fighting a war that we can never win.
你觉得他说的对吗
You think he's right?
那这一切又是为了什么?
So what's the point of all this, then?
不是街上的战争 是内心的战争
The war's not out there, it's in here.
你想不想继续战斗下去取决于你自己
Up to you how long you want to fight.
今天你干的不错
Good job today.
嘿
Hey.
你们怎么来了 来这干吗?
What's this, what are you guys doing?
来请我的朋友泰瑞喝一杯 你不来吗
Buying my friend Terri a drink, thought you might want to join us?
你还好吧?
You okay?
好吧 我要去...
Alright, I'm going to get a...
是的 很好
Yeah.
嘿 老大
Hey, Coach.
我想我可能用得上那段废话了
I think I can use that pep talk now.
你今天这样看起来还不错
You seemed to be doing fine on your own today.
不过我还是想跟你说一句 你不欠他什么
But, if I was, I'd tell you, you don't owe him anything, Daniel.
懂吗
You know that, right?
把我带成今天这么一个警察的人吗
Guy made me the cop I am today.
不 你是凭你自己变成这么一个警察的
No. You made the cop that you are today.
当然还有我们帮了点忙
With a little help from us.
怎么了
What?
谢谢
Thanks, man.
没事
No problem.
- 能来杯酒啤酒吗 - 当然
- Hey can I get a beer? - Sure.
那么
So.
现在说还是等会说
Do you want to talk about it now or later?
等会吧
Later. Okay?
我在这等你
I'm not going anywhere.